<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nightingale – FAQ</title>
    <link>/en/docs/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FAQ on Nightingale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="/en/docs/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Drawing related</title>
      <link>/en/docs/faq/graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/docs/faq/graph/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h4 id=&#34;q1the-monitoring-indicators-have-been-sent-to-the-server-but-in-the-end-the-graph-cannot-be-seen&#34;&gt;Q1:The monitoring indicators have been sent to the server, but in the end the graph cannot be seen&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this case, the data format is generally incorrect, or the data is not reported to the server.Suppose the sent index is n9e.points.in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First look at the transfer and tsdb modules for n9e.points.in error logs
Log in to the machine where the transfer is deployed and execute &lt;code&gt;tail -f /home/n9e/logs/transfer/WARNING.log|grep n9e.points.in&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br&gt;
登Lu to the machine where tsdb is deployed, execute &lt;code&gt;tail -f /home/n9e/logs/tsdb/WARNING.log|grep n9e.points.in&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If there is no error message, confirm again whether the monitoring index is reported to the server, and modify the transfer log level to DEBUG&lt;br&gt;
excute &lt;code&gt;tail -f /home/n9e/logs/transfer/DEBUG.log|grep n9e.points.in&lt;/code&gt; If no log appears, it means that it has not been reported to the server, and troubleshoot the sender&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;q2the-monitoring-plugin-is-placed-in-the-specified-directory-but-the-picture-cannot-be-seen-in-the-end&#34;&gt;Q2:The monitoring plugin is placed in the specified directory, but the picture cannot be seen in the end&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encounter this kind of problem is generally because the plugin execution failed.For example, the plug-in does not have executable permissions, or the data format reported by the plug-in is incorrect.You can log in to the machine in question and check /home/n9e/logs/collector/ERROR.log,Check whether there are error logs related to the plug-in, and if so, resolve them. If there is no error log, follow [Q1] (# q1 monitoring indicators have been sent to the server but the picture cannot be seen eventually)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;q3write-a-program-and-report-the-data-to-the-collector-or-transfer-according-to-data-specification-usagemetric-but-you-cannot-see-the-picture&#34;&gt;Q3:Write a program and report the data to the collector or transfer according to [Data Specification] (../usage/metric/), but you cannot see the picture&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First, print out the request body and resp body of the program. Check the err in the resp. If it is not empty, there is a problem with the report format. If the request body is empty, there is no data reported.
2.If the report is normal, check according to the idea of ​​[Q1] (# q1 monitoring indicators have been sent to the server but the picture cannot be seen eventually)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;q4log-process-or-port-collection-is-configured-but-the-relevant-monitoring-chart-cannot-be-seen&#34;&gt;Q4:Log, process or port collection is configured, but the relevant monitoring chart cannot be seen&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check whether the collection strategy has been delivered to the collector of the target machine    &lt;br&gt;
&lt;code&gt;curl IP of target machine:2058/api/collector/stra&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you can check the configured collection result, run tail -f /home/n9e/logs/collector/ERROR.log to check whether there is an error log&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If there is an error, follow the log prompt to deal with it. If no error is reported, follow [Q1] (# q1 monitoring indicators have been sent to the server but the picture cannot be seen in the end).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Alarm related</title>
      <link>/en/docs/faq/alert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/docs/faq/alert/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;q1the-alarm-strategy-has-been-configured-and-the-monitoring-indicators-are-abnormal-but-no-alarm-has-been-sended&#34;&gt;Q1:The alarm strategy has been configured, and the monitoring indicators are abnormal but no alarm has been sended?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May be the following situations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View object mount&lt;/strong&gt;：The object (usually a machine) needs to be mounted under the node (or its descendants) that configures the policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View monitoring data&lt;/strong&gt;：Confirm that the monitoring data corresponding to the monitoring strategy is valuable and will definitely trigger the threshold&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incorrect threshold setting&lt;/strong&gt;：Check the alarm function settings of the alarm strategy, confirm whether the alarm trigger condition is met, and confirm whether the effective time of the strategy is met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy is blocked&lt;/strong&gt;：Check the alarm policy blocking list to confirm whether the policy is blocked&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notify gateway problems&lt;/strong&gt;：On the alarm history page, check whether there is an alarm event that has been generated. If there is an alarm event, the problem is to notify the gateway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Issue of strategy&lt;/strong&gt;：
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run &lt;code&gt;curl &#39;127.0.0.1: 5800 /api /portal /stras /effective? All = 1&#39;&lt;/code&gt; to get a list of all strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the list does not have this strategy, check the monapi logs to see if there are any error messages. If there are errors, follow the prompts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If so, check the judge_instance field, find out which instance of the judge the strategy is distributed to, and log in to the machine where the judge is located,
Run &lt;code&gt;curl 127.0.0.1: 5840 /api /judge /stra /: id&lt;/code&gt; to see if it has been sent to judge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;judge解析策略异常&lt;/strong&gt;：Check the judge WARNING.log and ERROR.log logs to check if there is any error message for this strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;judge没有收到数据&lt;/strong&gt;：Modify the judge log level to DEBUG, &lt;code&gt;tail -f DEBUG.log | grep monitoring indicator&lt;/code&gt; No log output, indicating that the data has not reached the step of judge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;查看数据链路&lt;/strong&gt;：Check the transfer log and analyze why the data is not transferred from the transfer to the judge module&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
